Gould, William B., IV,NLRB Papers 6391
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- 501-03 Speech File: Statement o Auciello Iron Works, Inc. v. NLRB, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  NLRB Press Release no.R-2143, June 3, 1996. Supreme Court No.95-668, Washington, D.C.
- 501-03 Speech File: "Employee Participation and Labor Policy: Why the TEAM Act Should be Defeated and the National Labor Relations Act Amended", 1996 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  NLRB Press Release no.R-2145, June 6, 1996. Nebraska Bar Association Labor and Employment Law Section, Omaha, NE
- 501-03 Speech File: Statement on Fiscal Year 1997 Authorization, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  NLRB Press Release no.R-2147, June 13, 1996. Washington, D.C.
- 501-03 Speech File: "Initiatives by the Clinton Labor Board to Streamline Agency Procedures and Promote Stable Labor-Management Relations", 1996 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  NLRB Press Release no.R-2151, June 26, 1996. The Pennsylvania State University's Jobs and Justice Towards Improving the Employment Relationship, An International Symposium, State College, PA
- 501-03 Speech File: Statement by William B. Gould IV Chairman, National Labor Relations Board, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  NLRB Press Release no.R-2153, July 11, 1996. Washington, D.C.
- 501-03 Speech File: "The Accomplishments and Legacy of Jack Henning as Leader of the California Labor Federation", 1996 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  NLRB Press Release no.R-2157, July 30, 1996. California Labor Federation, AFL-CIO, 21st Biennial Convention, Los Angeles, CA
- 501-03 Speech File: Statement Before the Committee on Labor and Human Resources of the United States Senate, Oversight Hearing on the National Labor Relations Board, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  September 17, 1996. Washington, D.C.
- 501-03 Speech File: Book Four: Chairman Gould Speeches (Box 6, Folder 58)
  Fiscal Year 1997 - Index
- 501-03 Speech File: "Assessing the Work of the U.N. War Crimes Tribunals", 1996 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  NLRB Press Release no.R-2177, October 11, 1996. Introduction of the Honorable Richard J. Goldstone, Stanford Law School, Stanford, CA
- 501-03 Speech File: "John P. Kennedy Named to NLRB Management Advisory Panel", 1996 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  NLRB Press Release no.R- 2178, October 23, 1996. Washington, D.C.
- 501-03 Speech File: "Promotion of Cooperative Relationships Between Labor and Management: Policies of the National Labor Relations Board", 1996 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  NLRB Press Release no.R-2179, October 25, 1996. American Forest and Paper Association Southern Conference, Fall Meeting, Atlanta, GA
- 501-03 Speech File: "Searching for the Middle Ground in 1997 to Foster Harmonious Labor-Management Relations", 1996 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  NLRB Press Release no.R-2190. December 21, 1996. In Observance of the Stetson University College of Law Fall Graduation Ceremony, St. Petersburg, FL
- 501-03 Speech File: "NLRB Chairman Gould Anticipates a Cooperative and Constructive Relationship with Congress in 1997", 1996 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  NLRB Press Release no.R-2191, December 21, 1996. St. Petersburg, FL
- 501-03 Speech File: "Recent Developments at the National Labor Relations Board", 1996 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  Saint Louis University Law Jounal, v.40:no.1 (1996:Winter)
- 501-03 Speech File: "in 3-Year Report, NLRB Chairman Gould Assesses Agency Decisions, Initiatives; Sees Progress in Labor Relations Environment", 1997 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  NLRB Press Release no.R-2202, March 7, 1997. Washington, D.C.
- 501-03 Speech File: "A Tribute", 1997 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  NLRB Press Release no.R-2211, March 18, 1997. In Observance of William R. Stewart's Retirement from the National Labor Relations Board, Washington, D.C.
- 501-03 Speech File: "Autonomy and Intervention: Some Parts of the National Labor Relations Act Paradox", 1997 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  NLRB Press Release no.R-2210; March 20, 1997. Stetson University College of Law, The Center for Dispute Resolution, Twelfth Annual National Conference on Labor and Employment Law, Clearwater, FL
- 501-03 Speech File: "Alternative Dispute Resolution and the National Labor Relations Board: Some Ruminations About Emerging Legal Issues, Jose Canseco and Gertrude Stein", 1997 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  NLRB Press Release no.R-2213, April 8, 1997. Greater Bay Chapter of the Industrial Relations Research Association, I.R.R.A. Inaugural Luncheon, Oakland, CA
- 501-03 Speech File: "Labor Relations For the 21st Century", 1997 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  NLRB Press Release no.R-2253, April 14, 1997. Speech Before the Baruch College National Center for the Study of Collective Bargaining in Higher Education and the Professionals "Silver Anniversary Conference", New York, NY
- 501-03 Speech File: NLRB Chairman Urges Grads "To Advance the Public Good", 1997 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  NLRB Press Release no.R-2220, May 25, 1997. Columbus, OH
- 501-03 Speech File: "The Adminstration of U.S. Labor Law and Efforts at Procedural Reforms at the National Labor Relations Board", 1997 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  NLRB Press Release no.R-2221, May 27, 1997. Speech Before the Association of Danish Labor Law, Copenhagen, Demark
- 501-03 Speech File: "A Tale of Two Centrist Countries: Taft-Hartley, The Thatcher Reforms, 1997 and All That" (Box 6, Folder 72)
  NLRB Press Release no.R-2222, June 2, 1997. Speech Before the Royal Institute of International Affairs, London, England
- 501-03 Speech File: "Labor-Management Cooperation and NLRB Administrative Reforms", 1997 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  NLRB Press Release no.R- 2227, June 11, 1997. Thirteenth Annual Alabama Governor's Labor-Management Conference, Gulf Shores, AL
- 501-03 Speech File: "Installation Remarks", 1997 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  NLRB Press Release no.R-2233, June 18, 1997. In Observance of the Occasion of the Installation of Dorothy Moore-Duncan as Regional Director of the National Labor Relations Board, Region 4, Philadelphia, PA
- 501-03 Speech File: "NLRB Chairman Gould Announces Board's Vote to Seek Injunctive Relief in Detroit Newspapers Case", 1997 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  NLRB Press Release no.R-2238, July 1, 1997. Washington, D.C.
- 501-03 Speech File: "In Honor of the Bestowing of the President's Award for Distinguished Federal Civilian Service Upon William R. Stewart, Former Chief Counsel to Chairman Gould", 1997 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  NLRB Press Release no.R-2241, July 21, 1997. Washington, D.C.
- 501-03 Speech File: Statement Before the Subcommittee on Human Resources of the Committee on Government Reform and Oversight, U.S. House of Representatives, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  July 24, 1997. Washington, D.C.
- 501-03 Speech File: "Labor Policy By and Beyond the NLRB: Globalization, Corporate Reorganization, and the American Workforce", 1997 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  NLRB Press Release no.R-2245, August 4, 1997. Before the Commonwealth Club of California, San Francisco, CA
- 501-03 Speech File: "Assessing Taft-Hartley's Impact on Labor-Management Balance", 1997 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  NLRB Press Release no.R- 2254, September 9, 1997. Ceremony on the Occasion of the 50th Anniversary of Shaw and Rosenthal, Baltimore, MD
- Speech: "Tribute to Jack Sheinkman", 1994 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  November 2, 1994. The Jack Sheinkman Endowment Fund Dinner, New York, NY
- Speech: "A Memoir of New Jersey and Long Lost Youth", 1998 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  May 19, 1998. Rutgers School of Management and Labor Relations Reception and Dinner in Recognition of William B. Gould IV's Receipt of an Honorary Degree from Rutgers Univerisity, New Brunswick, NJ
- Speech: "The Unwinding Trail: Some Reflections on the Life and Times of William Benjamin Gould", 1998 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  December 15, 1998. Speech at the New Hanoverr County Public Library, Wilmington, NC
- Gould Speech Citations, Including Index (folder 1 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 83)
- Gould Speech Citations, Including Index (folder 2 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 84)
- Gould's Baseball Service Statements, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 85)
- Gould Statements, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 86)
- Personal Correspondences (Box 6, Folder 87)
- Agenda for Reform Book Reviews, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 88)
- A Briefing for the Commission on the Future of Worker-Management Relations, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 89)
- Commission o nth Future of Worker-Management Relations, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 90)
- Current Law is a Barrier to Workplace Cooperation Just Ask the Current Chairman of the NLRB, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 91)
- IAM-Bath Iron Workers Conference, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 92)
- Telephone Message From Frank McCulloch, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 93)
- Susan Quinn, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 94)
- Former NLRB Chair Reflects on Washington's Brutal Ways, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 95)
- Beck Decisions, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Articles About Gould Confirmation (folder 1 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Articles About Gould Confirmation (folder 2 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Articles About Gould Post-Confirmation (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Articles by Gould (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Articles About NLRB (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Articles Generally About Labor (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Articles Miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Senate Bill to Amend the Fair Labor Relations Act of 1938 S. 1722, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Fairness for Small Businesses and Players Act of 1998 HR 3245 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- United Mine Workers, Peaker Run Coal Company (Box 7, Folder 11)
  February 10, 1977
- United Mine Workers, US Court of Appeals (Box 7, Folder 12)
  Contempt Adjudication. April 21, 1987
- United Mine Workers and John L. Bagwell (Box 7, Folder 13)
  Authorization to File an Amicus Brief. July 13, 1993.
- United Mine Workers Labor Organization Annual Report (Box 7, Folder 14)
  LM-2. August 9, 1993.
- United Mine Workers, District 28 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  Briefs before the US Supreme Court.
- United Mine Workers, NLRB no.162 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- United Mine Workers, NLRB no.162 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- United Mine Workers, Bill Usery Associates (Box 7, Folder 17)
  March 23, 1994.
- Authorization to Initiate Contempt Proceedings Against the United Mine Workers (Box 7, Folder 18)
  April 15, 1994
- United Mine Workers, US Court of Appeals (Box 7, Folder 19)
  Petition for Adjudication in Civil Contempt. April 21, 1994.
- Labor Board Asks Court to Fine United Mine Workers (Box 7, Folder 20)
  May 3, 1994.
- United Mine Workers, Certiorari to the Supreme Court of Virginia (Box 7, Folder 21)
  June 30, 1994.
- United Mine Workers, Bagwell Notes (Box 7, Folder 22)
  July 22, 1994.
- United Mine Workers, US Court of Appeals (Box 7, Folder 23)
  NLRB Response to Citation of Additional Authority. August 3, 1994.
- United Mine Workers, US Court of Appeals (Box 7, Folder 24)
  Second Amended Petition for Adjudication in Civil Contempt. December 9, 1994.
- Status of Settlement Discussion with the United Mine Workers (Box 7, Folder 25)
  December 16, 1994.
- United Mine Workers Trial Schedule (Box 7, Folder 26)
- United Mine Workers, US Court of Appeals (Box 7, Folder 27)
  Order. January 9, 1995.
- United Mine Workers, US Court of Appeals (Box 7, Folder 28)
  Report of Special Master on Settlement Conference. January 31, 1995.
- What We need At a Minimum in United Mine Workers Settlement (Box 7, Folder 29)
- United Mine Workers Contempt Case Correspondence and Memorandums (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Teamsters Local 115, US Court of Appeals (Box 7, Folder 31)
  Report and Recommendation. October 12, 1994.
- Teamsters Local 115, US Court of Appeals (Box 7, Folder 32)
  Respondents' Objections. November 18, 1994.
- Teamsters Local 115, US Court of Appeals (Box 7, Folder 33)
  NLRB Response to Respondents' Objections. December 5, 1994.
- Teamsters Local 115, US Court of Appeals (Box 7, Folder 34)
  Order. January 13, 1995.
- Teamsters Local 115, US Court of Appeals (Box 7, Folder 35)
  Suggestion for Rehearing En Banc. January 25, 1995.
- Teamsters Local 115, US Court of Appeals (Box 7, Folder 36)
  Contempt Adjudication. July 20, 1995.
- Teamsters Local 115 Brief for the National Labor Relations Board in Opposition (Box 7, Folder 37)
  March, 1996.
- Teamsters Local 115 Correspondence and Memorandums (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Ellis Boal and "Labor Notes" (Box 7, Folder 39)
- News Clippings: Chairman's and General Counsel's First Six Months, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Government Performance and Results Act (GPRA) Testimony Binder (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Folder 1 of 3
- Government Performance and Results Act (GPRA) Testimony Binder (Box 8, Folder 3)
  Folder 2 of 3
- Government Performance and Results Act (GPRA) Testimony Binder (Box 8, Folder 4)
  Folder 3 of 3
- 103-343 Gould Nomination Hearing, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- 104-15 Hearing on Execution Order 12954, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- 104-655 Hearing on Examining the Activities and Progress of the NLRR, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Petition for Rulemaking to Provide Weingarten-type Rights to Employees in Nonunion Workplaces, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- NLRB Case No. 19-RC-13220 Grandview Health System Supervisory Status, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Foreign Language Elections, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Mail Ballot Elections, 1994-1998 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- NLRB Case No. 19-RC-12815 Golden Alaska Seafoods Mail Ballot Election, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- NLRB No. 11-RC-6076 Smith Enterprises Mail Ballot Election, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- NLRB Case No. 18-RC-15735 Metz Baking Mail Ballot Election, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- NLRB Case No. 19-RD-3198 Northwest Marble & Terrazzo, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  Mail Ballot Election
- NLRB Case No. 27-RC-7569 Piquniq Management, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- NLRB Case No. 29-RC-8458 G.S.N. Trucking, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- NLRB Case No. 30-RD-1160 Laidlaw Transit, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  Mail Ballot Elections
- NLRB Case No. 30-RC-5686 Single Source Transportation, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- NLRB Case No. 36-RC-5661 Fred Meyer, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- NLRB Case No. 8-RC-21718 Family Service Society of Yonkers, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- NLRB Case No. 19-RC-13199 Sears Roebuck Mail Ballot Election, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- NLRB Case No. 19-RC-13235 G. D. Chilcott, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- NLRB Case No. 4-RC-18987 Weis Markets, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- NLRB Case No. 19-RC-13474 Space Mark, Inc., 1997 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- NLRB Case No. 10-RD-1278 Alltel Georgia Communications, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- NLRB Case No. 13-RC-19484 Consolidated Freightways, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- NLRB Case No. 18-RC-16043 Budget Rent-a-Car, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- NLRB Case No. 8-RC-15541; 15542 Ford Motor Company, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- NLRB Case no. 25-RC-9629 V. G. Express, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- NLRB Case No. GR-7-RM-1421; 1422 Community Action Agency of South Central Michigan, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Kenneth M. Burke OIG-I-173 and OIG-I-187, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Section 14(b) of the NLRA/Preemption, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- NLRB Case No. 36-RD-1434 Lone Star Northwest, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- NLRB Case No. 10-RC-14179 Shepard Convention Services, Inc., 1994 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Regional Management Conference, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Waiver or Stuatory Right to Bargain (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Beck Cases, 1996-1998 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Michael B. Waitzkin "At Will Employment", 1997 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Starting Over: The Presidential Appointment Process, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 40)
- OIG-I-190, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 41)
- OIG-I-192, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 42)
- Dispute Concerning Dynastic and the Inspector General's Office (Box 8, Folder 43)
- FOIA Request and Appeal, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 44)
- Congressional Record, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 45)